Guide to the William Leonard Albrecht Papers 1880-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Albrecht Furniture Company, 1886-1968; Series I; 47.25 linear feet, 113 oversize volumes, and 3 oversize tubes
  - General Correspondence, 1936-1968; Subseries 4; 30.0 linear feet
    - I, 1957 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - J, 1957 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - K, 1957 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1957 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Levin Brothers, 1957 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - L, 1957 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1957 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - M, 1957 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - N, 1957 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Philadelphia Carpet Company, 1957 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - P, 1957 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Q, 1957 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - R, 1957 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Salisbury Company, 1957 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Spinning Wheel, 1957 (Box-folder 62/17)
    - S, 1957 (Box-folder 62/18)
    - T, 1957 (Box-folder 62/19)
    - U, 1957 (Box-folder 62/20)
    - V, 1957 (Box-folder 62/21)
    - W, 1957 (Box-folder 62/22)
    - Y, 1957 (Box-folder 62/23)
    - Albrecht, 1958 (Box-folder 62/24)
    - A, 1958 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - B, 1958 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1958 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - C, 1958 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1958 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - D, 1958 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - E, 1958 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - F, 1958 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Grand Rapids Furniture Makers Guild, 1958 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - G, 1958 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - H, 1958 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1958 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - I, 1958 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - J, 1958, 1958 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - K, 1958 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1958 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Levin Brothers, 1958 (Box-folder 63/17)
    - Lewisburg Chair and Furniture, 1958 (Box-folder 63/18)
    - L, 1958 (Box-folder 63/19)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1958 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - M, 1958 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - N, 1958 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - O, 1958 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Philadelphia Carpet Company, 1958 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - P, 1958 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - R, 1958 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Salisbury Company, 1958 (Box-folder 64/8)
    - S, 1958 (Box-folder 64/9)
    - T, 1958 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - U, 1958 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - V, 1958 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - Y, 1958 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - Albrecht, 1959 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - A, 1959 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - B, 1959 (Box-folder 64/16)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1959 (Box-folder 64/17)
    - C, 1959 (Box-folder 64/18)
    - Dearborn Company, 1959 (Box-folder 64/19)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1959 (Box-folder 64/20)
    - Dunbar Furniture Company, 1959 (Box-folder 64/21)
    - D, 1959 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - E, 1959 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - F, 1959 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - G, 1959 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - H, 1959 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1959 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - I, 1959 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - J, 1959 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - K, 1959 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1959 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Levin Brothers, 1959 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Lewisburg Chair and Furniture Company, 1959 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - L, 1959 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1959 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - M, 1959 (Box-folder 65/15)
    - N, 1959 (Box-folder 65/16)
    - O, 1959 (Box-folder 65/17)
    - P, 1959 (Box-folder 65/18)
    - R, 1959 (Box-folder 65/19)
    - Salisbury Company, 1959 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - S, 1959 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - T, 1959 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - U, 1959 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - V, 1959 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - W, 1959 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Y, Z, 1959 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - A, 1960 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - B, 1960 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - C, 1960 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Dearborn Company, 1960 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Drexel Furniture, 1960 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - D, 1960 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - E, 1960 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - F, 1960 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - G, 1960 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - H, 1960 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1960 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - I, 1960 (Box-folder 66/19)
    - J, 1960 (Box-folder 66/20)
    - K, 1960 (Box-folder 66/21)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1960 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Levin Brothers, 1960 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Lewisburg Chair and Furniture, 1960 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - L, 1960 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1960 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - M, 1960 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - N, 1960 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - O, 1960 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - P, 1960 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - R, 1960 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Salisbury Company, 1960 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - S, 1960 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - T, 1960 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - U, 1960 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - V, 1960 (Box-folder 67/15)
    - W, 1960 (Box-folder 67/16)
    - X - Z, 1960 (Box-folder 67/17)
    - A, 1961 (Box-folder 67/18)
    - B, 1961 (Box-folder 67/19)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1961 (Box-folder 67/20)
    - C, 1961 (Box-folder 67/21)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1961 (Box-folder 67/22)
    - D, 1961 (Box-folder 67/23)
    - F, 1961 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - G, 1961 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - H, 1961 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1961 (Box-folder 68/4)
    - I, 1961 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - J, 1961 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - K, 1961 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1961 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Levin Brothers, 1961 (Box-folder 68/9)
    - L, 1961 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1961 (Box-folder 68/11)
    - M, 1961 (Box-folder 68/12)
    - N, 1961 (Box-folder 68/13)
    - O, 1961 (Box-folder 68/14)
    - P, 1961 (Box-folder 68/15)
    - R, 1961 (Box-folder 68/16)
    - Salisbury Company, 1961 (Box-folder 68/17)
    - S, 1961 (Box-folder 68/18)
    - T, 1961 (Box-folder 68/19)
    - U, 1961 (Box-folder 68/20)
    - V, 1961 (Box-folder 68/21)
    - W, 1961 (Box-folder 68/22)
    - Y, 1961 (Box-folder 68/23)
    - Albrecht, 1962 (Box-folder 68/24)
    - A, 1962 (Box-folder 68/25)
    - B, 1962 (Box-folder 68/26)
    - C, 1962 (Box-folder 68/27)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1962 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - D, 1962 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - E, 1962 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - F, 1962 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - G, 1962 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - H, 1962 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - I, 1962 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - J, 1962 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - K, 1962 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1962 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Levin Brothers, 1962 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - Lewisburg Chair Company, 1962 (Box-folder 69/12)
    - L, 1962 (Box-folder 69/13)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1962 (Box-folder 69/14)
    - M, 1962 (Box-folder 69/15)
    - N, 1962 (Box-folder 69/16)
    - O, 1962 (Box-folder 69/17)
    - P, 1962 (Box-folder 69/18)
    - R, 1962 (Box-folder 69/19)
    - Salisbury Company, 1962 (Box-folder 69/20)
    - S, 1962 (Box-folder 69/21)
    - T, 1962 (Box-folder 69/22)
    - U, 1962 (Box-folder 69/23)
    - V, 1962 (Box-folder 69/24)
    - W, 1962 (Box-folder 69/25)
    - X - Z, 1962 (Box-folder 69/26)
    - Albrecht, 1963 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - A, 1963 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - James Battin, 1963 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - B, 1963 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1963 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - C, 1963 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1963 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - D, 1963 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - E, 1963 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - F, 1963 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - G, 1963 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - H, 1963 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - I, 1963 (Box-folder 70/13)
    - J, 1963 (Box-folder 70/14)
    - K, 1963 (Box-folder 70/15)
    - 1963, James Lees and Sons (Box-folder 70/16)
    - Levin Brothers, 1963 (Box-folder 70/17)
    - Lewisburg Chair Company, 1963 (Box-folder 70/18)
    - L, 1963 (Box-folder 70/19)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1963 (Box-folder 70/20)
    - M, 1963 (Box-folder 70/21)
    - N, 1963 (Box-folder 70/22)
    - O, 1963 (Box-folder 70/23)
    - P, 1963 (Box-folder 70/24)
    - R, 1963 (Box-folder 70/25)
    - Salisbury Company, 1963 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - S, 1963 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - T, 1963 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - U, 1963 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - V, 1963 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - W, 1963 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Y, 1963 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Albrecht, 1964 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - A, 1964 (Box-folder 71/9)
    - James F. Battin, 1964 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - B, 1964 (Box-folder 71/11)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1964 (Box-folder 71/12)
    - C, 1964 (Box-folder 71/13)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1964 (Box-folder 71/14)
    - D, 1964 (Box-folder 71/15)
    - E, 1964 (Box-folder 71/16)
    - F, 1964 (Box-folder 71/17)
    - G, 1964 (Box-folder 71/18)
    - H, 1964 (Box-folder 71/19)
    - I, 1964 (Box-folder 71/20)
    - J, 1964 (Box-folder 71/21)
    - K, 1964 (Box-folder 71/22)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1964 (Box-folder 71/23)
    - Levin Brothers, 1964 (Box-folder 71/24)
    - Lewisburg Chair Company, 1964 (Box-folder 71/25)
    - L, 1964 (Box-folder 71/26)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1964 (Box-folder 71/27)
    - M, 1964 (Box-folder 71/28)
    - N, 1964 (Box-folder 71/29)
    - O, 1964 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - P, 1964 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - R, 1964 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Salisbury Company, 1964 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - S, 1964 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - T, 1964 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - U, 1964 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - V, 1964 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - W, 1964 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Albrecht, 1965 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - A, 1965 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - B, 1965 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - C, 1965 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1965 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - D, 1965 (Box-folder 72/15)
    - E, 1965 (Box-folder 72/16)
    - F, 1965 (Box-folder 72/17)
    - G, 1965 (Box-folder 72/18)
    - H, 1965 (Box-folder 72/19)
    - J, 1965 (Box-folder 72/20)
    - K, 1965 (Box-folder 72/21)
    - Levin Brothers, 1965 (Box-folder 72/22)
    - L, 1965 (Box-folder 72/23)
    - M, 1965 (Box-folder 72/24)
    - N, 1965 (Box-folder 72/25)
    - O, 1965 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - P, 1965 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - R, 1965 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Salisbury Company, 1965 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - S, 1965 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - T, 1965 (Box-folder 73/6)
    - U, 1965 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - V, 1965 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - W, 1965 (Box-folder 73/9)
    - Albrecht, 1966 (Box-folder 73/10)
    - A, 1966 (Box-folder 73/11)
    - B, 1966 (Box-folder 73/12)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box-folder 73/13)
    - C, 1966 (Box-folder 73/14)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1966 (Box-folder 73/15)
    - D, 1966 (Box-folder 73/16)
    - E, 1966 (Box-folder 73/17)
    - F, 1966 (Box-folder 73/18)
    - G, 1966 (Box-folder 73/19)
    - H, 1966 (Box-folder 73/20)
    - I, 1966 (Box-folder 73/21)
    - J, 1966 (Box-folder 73/22)
    - K, 1966 (Box-folder 73/23)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1966 (Box-folder 73/24)
    - Levin Brothers, 1966 (Box-folder 73/25)
    - L, 1966 (Box-folder 73/26)
    - M, 1966 (Box-folder 73/27)
    - N, 1966 (Box-folder 73/28)
    - O, 1966 (Box-folder 73/29)
    - P, 1966 (Box-folder 73/30)
    - R, 1966 (Box-folder 73/31)
    - Salisbury Company, 1966 (Box-folder 73/32)
    - S, 1966 (Box-folder 73/33)
    - T, 1966 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - U, V, 1966 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - W - Z, 1966 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Albrecht, 1967 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - A, 1967 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - B, 1967 (Box-folder 74/6)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - C, 1967 (Box-folder 74/8)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1967 (Box-folder 74/9)
    - 1967, D (Box-folder 74/10)
    - E, 1967 (Box-folder 74/11)
    - F, 1967 (Box-folder 74/12)
    - G, 1967 (Box-folder 74/13)
    - H, 1967 (Box-folder 74/14)
    - I, 1967 (Box-folder 74/15)
    - K, 1967 (Box-folder 74/16)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1967 (Box-folder 74/17)
    - Levin Brothers, 1967 (Box-folder 74/18)
    - L, 1967 (Box-folder 74/19)
    - M, 1967 (Box-folder 74/20)
    - N, 1967 (Box-folder 74/21)
    - O, 1967 (Box-folder 74/22)
    - P, 1967 (Box-folder 74/23)
    - R, 1967 (Box-folder 74/24)
    - Salisbury Company, 1967 (Box-folder 74/25)
    - S, 1967 (Box-folder 74/26)
    - T, 1967 (Box-folder 74/27)
    - U, 1967 (Box-folder 74/28)
    - V, 1967 (Box-folder 74/29)
    - W, 1967 (Box-folder 74/30)
    - Y, 1967 (Box-folder 74/31)
    - A - Z, 1968 (Box-folder 74/32)
  - Financial Records, 1886-1967; Subseries 5; 5.0 linear feet and 113 oversize volumes
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, A-E, 1935-1943 (Volume 75)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, F-K, 1935-1943 (Volume 76)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, L-P, 1935-1943 (Volume 77)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, Q-Z, 1935-1943 (Volume 78)
    - Accounts Receivable List, 1890-1898 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Insurance, 1932-1944 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Insurance, 1945-1967 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - Inventory, 1888-1894 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - Inventory, 1897 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - Inventory, 1900 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Inventory, 1902 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - Inventory, 1910 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Inventory, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Inventory, 1913-1915 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - Inventory, 1913 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Inventory, 1914 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Inventory, 1917 (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Inventory, 1918 (Box-folder 80/7)
    - Inventory, 1919 (Box-folder 80/8)
    - Inventory, 1920 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - Inventory, 1921 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Inventory, 1922 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Inventory, 1923 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - Inventory, 1925 (Box-folder 81/4)
    - Inventory, 1926 (Box-folder 81/5)
    - Inventory, 1927 (Box-folder 81/6)
    - Inventory, 1929 (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Inventory, 1930 (Box-folder 81/8)
    - Inventory, 1931 (Box-folder 81/9)
    - Inventory, 1932 (Box-folder 81/10)
    - Inventory, 1942 (Box-folder 81/11)
    - Inventory, 1943 (Box-folder 81/12)
    - Inventory, 1944 (Box-folder 82/1)
    - Inventory, 1945 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - Inventory, 1946 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Inventory, 1950 (Box-folder 82/4)
    - Inventory, 1951 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - Inventory, 1955 (Box-folder 82/6)
    - Inventory, 1956 (Box-folder 82/7)
    - Inventory, 1957 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - Inventory, 1958 (Box-folder 82/9)
    - Inventory, 1959 (Box-folder 82/10)
    - Inventory, 1960 (Box-folder 82/11)
    - Inventory, 1961 (Box-folder 82/12)
    - Inventory, 1962 (Box-folder 82/13)
    - Inventory, 1963 (Box-folder 82/14)
    - Inventory, undated (Box-folder 82/15)
    - Record of Sales and Purchases, 1910-1931 (Box-folder 83/1)
    - Stock book, undated (Box-folder 83/2)
    - Taxes, 1930-1945 (Box-folder 83/3)
    - Taxes, 1946 (Box-folder 83/4)
    - Taxes, 1952 (Box-folder 83/5)
    - Taxes, 1953 (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Taxes, 1954 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - Taxes, 1955 (Box-folder 83/8)
    - Taxes, 1956 (Box-folder 83/9)
    - Taxes, 1958 (Box-folder 83/10)
    - Taxes, 1959 (Box-folder 83/11)
    - Taxes, 1960 (Box-folder 83/12)
    - Taxes, 1961 (Box-folder 83/13)
    - Taxes, 1963 (Box-folder 83/14)
    - Taxes, 1964 (Box-folder 83/15)
    - Taxes, 1965 (Box-folder 83/16)
    - Taxes, 1966 (Box-folder 83/17)
    - Taxes, 1967 (Box-folder 83/18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1895-1933 (Box-folder 83/19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 83/20)
    - General Journal, August 1886-May 1890 (Volume 1)
    - General Journal, June 1890-April 1893 (Volume 2)
    - General Journal, May 1893-September 1896 (Volume 3)
    - General Journal, September 1896 August 1898 (Volume 4)
    - General Journal, August 1898-October 1899 (Volume 5)
    - General Journal, November 1899-August 1901 (Volume 6)
    - General Journal, September 1901-December 1905 (Volume 7)
    - General Journal, 1906-1908 (Volume 8)
    - General Journal, January 1909-August 1910 (Volume 9)
    - General Journal, September 1910-August 1913 (Volume 10)
    - General Journal, September 1913-July 1915 (Volume 11)
    - General Journal, August 1915-December 1916 (Volume 12)
    - General Journal, 1917-1918 (Volume 13)
    - General Journal, January 1919-May 1920 (Volume 14)
    - General Journal, June 1920-November 1922 (Volume 15)
    - General Journal, December 1922-December 1925 (Volume 16)
    - General Journal, December 1925-December 1928 (Volume 17)
    - General Journal, December 1928-July 1930 (Volume 18)
    - General Journal, August 1930-April 1933 (Volume 19)
    - General Journal, April 1933-February 1935 (Volume 20)
    - General Journal, February-December 1935 (Volume 21)
    - Purchases Journal, August 1886-May 1890 (Volume 22)
    - Sales Journal, May-October 1888 (Volume 23)
    - Sales Journal, October 1888-July 1889 (Volume 24)
    - Sales Journal, July 1889-April 1890 (Volume 25)
    - Sales Journal, April-November 1890 (Volume 26)
    - Sales Journal, November 1890-May 1891 (Volume 27)
    - Sales Journal, June 1891-April 1892 (Volume 28)
    - Sales Journal, April 1892-June 1893 (Volume 29)
    - Sales Journal, June 1893-March 1894 (Volume 30)
    - Shipments, September 1903-June 1908 (Volume 31)
    - Shipments, June 1908-May 1915 (Volume 32)
    - Shipments, June 1915-November 1918 (Volume 33)
    - Shipments, December 1918-November 1921 (Volume 34)
    - Shipments, December 1921-October 1924 (Volume 35)
    - Shipments, December 1929-November 1933 (Volume 36)
    - Shipments, 1933-1936 (Volume 37)
    - Cash Journal, August 1886-September 1889 (Volume 38)
    - Cash Journal, October 1889-March 1891 (Volume 39)
    - Cash Journal, April 1891-March 1893 (Volume 40)
    - Cash Journal, March 1893-June 1895 (Volume 41)
    - Cash Journal, July 1895-November 1899 (Volume 42)
    - Cash Journal, December 1899-August 1907 (Volume 43)
    - Cash Journal, September 1907-December 1910 (Volume 44)
    - Cash Journal, 1911-1913 (Volume 45)
    - Cash Journal, January 1914-August 1916 (Volume 46)
    - Cash Journal, September 1916-December 1916 (Volume 47)
    - Cash Journal, January 1917-March 1919 (Volume 48)
    - Cash Journal, April 1919-June 1921 (Volume 49)
    - Cash Journal, July 1921-January 1923 (Volume 50)
    - Cash Journal, February 1923-April 1924 (Volume 51)
    - Cash Journal, April 1924-July 1925 (Volume 52)
    - Cash Journal, August 1925-November 1926 (Volume 53)
    - Cash Journal, December 1926-April 1928 (Volume 54)
    - Cash Journal, May 1928-June 1929 (Volume 55)
    - Cash Journal, July 1929-August 1930 (Volume 56)
    - Cash Journal, September 1930-March 1932 (Volume 57)
    - Cash Journal, April 1932-November 1933 (Volume 58)
    - Cash Journal, November 1933-October 1934 (Volume 59)
    - Cash Journal, November 1934-August 1935 (Volume 60)
    - Cash Journal, September-December 1935 (Volume 61)
    - Petty Cash, May 1890-September 1891 (Volume 62)
    - Petty Cash, September 1891-October 1892 (Volume 63)
    - Petty Cash, November 1892-March 1894 (Volume 64)
    - General Ledger, 1891-1905 (Volume 65)
    - General Ledger, 1906-1912 (Volume 66)
    - General Ledger, 1913-1916 (Volume 67)
    - General Ledger, 1917-1927 (Volume 68)
    - General Ledger, 1928-1930 (Volume 69)
    - General Ledger, 1931-1934 (Volume 70)
    - General Ledger, 1935-1936 (Volume 71)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1888-1891 (Volume 72)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1892-1895 (Volume 73)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1896-1899 (Volume 74)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1905-1909 (Volume 76)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1910-1913 (Volume 77)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1914-1916 (Volume 78)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1917-1919 (Volume 79)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1920-1923 (Volume 80)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1924-1927 (Volume 81)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1928-1930 (Volume 82)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1931-1934 (Volume 83)
    - Bills Payable Ledger, January-February 1919 (Volume 84)
    - Bills Receivable Ledger, undated (Volume 85)
    - List of Marriage Licenses, January 1929-May 1933 (Volume 86)
    - List of Building Permits, March 1929-February 1933 (Volume 87)
    - Cash Receipts, 1936-1940, Check Register, 1936-1940, Payroll Register, 1936-1940, Sales Journal, 1936-1940, Purchases Journal, 1936-1940, General Journal, 1936-1940 (Volume 88)
    - Cash Receipts, 1941-1944, Check Register, 1941-1944, Payroll Register, 1941-1944, Sales Journal, 1941-1944, Purchases Journal, 1941-1944, General Journal, 1941-1944 (Volume 89)
    - Invoices, November 1895-March 1898 (Volume 90)
    - Invoices, April 1898-October 1899 (Volume 91)
    - Invoices, November 1899-April 1901 (Volume 92)
    - Invoices, May 1901-May 1903 (Volume 93)
    - Invoices, June 1903-December 1905 (Volume 94)
    - Invoices, 1906-1907 (Volume 95)
    - Invoices, January 1908-August 1909 (Volume 96)
    - Invoices, August 1909-March 1911 (Volume 97)
    - Invoices, April 1911-December 1912 (Volume 98)
    - Invoices, January 1913-March 1914 (Volume 99)
    - Invoices, April 1914-December 1915 (Volume 100)
    - Invoices, December 1916-June 1918 (Volume 101)
    - Invoices, June 1918-October 1919 (Volume 102)
    - Invoices, November 1919-May 1921 (Volume 103)
    - Invoices, May 1921-November 1922 (Volume 104)
    - Invoices, December 1922-September 1924 (Volume 105)
    - Invoices, October 1924-May 1926 (Volume 106)
    - Invoices, May 1926-October 1927 (Volume 107)
    - Invoices, October 1927 November 1928 (Volume 108)
    - Invoices, December 1928-February 1930 (Volume 109)
    - Invoices, February 1930-October 1931 (Volume 110)
    - Invoices, October 1931-September 1933 (Volume 111)
    - Invoices, October 1933-October 1934 (Volume 112)
    - Invoices, October 1934-December 1935 (Volume 113)
  - Legal Documents, 1908-1962; Subseries 6; 0.5 linear feet
    - Certificates and Licenses, 1908-1938 (Box-folder 83/21)
    - Employee Agreements, 1930-1947 (Box-folder 83/22)
    - Employee Agreements, 1948 (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Employee Agreements, 1953 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Employee Agreements, 1949 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Employee Agreements, 1950 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - Employee Agreements, 1951 (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Employee Agreements, 1952 (Box-folder 84/6)
    - Employee Agreements, 1954 (Box-folder 84/7)
    - Employee Agreements, 1955 (Box-folder 84/8)
    - Employee Agreements, 1956 (Box-folder 84/9)
    - Employee Agreements, 1959 (Box-folder 84/10)
    - Employee Agreements, 1961 (Box-folder 84/11)
    - Employee Agreements, 1962 (Box-folder 84/12)
    - Property Mortgage, 1934 (Box-folder 84/13)
  - Advertising and Organizational, 1935-1964; Subseries 7; 0.25 linear feet and 3 oversize tubes
    - Advertising, circa 1950 (Box-folder 84/14)
    - Furniture Catalog, 1940 (Box-folder 84/15)
    - Radio Ads, 1936 (Box-folder 84/16)
    - Radio Ads, 1937 (Box-folder 84/17)
    - Radio Ads, 1938 (Box-folder 84/18)
    - Radio Ads, 1939 (Box-folder 84/19)
    - Radio Ads, 1940 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - Radio Ads, 1941 (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Radio Ads, 1944 (Box-folder 85/3)
    - Newspaper Ad, 1937 (Box-folder 85/4)
    - Blank Checks, circa 1935 (Box-folder 85/5)
    - Building Plans and Furniture Guide, undated (Box-folder 85/6)
    - Albrecht Building Plan, undated (Box-folder OS1/1)
    - Albrecht Furniture Company, Sign Plan, undated (Box-folder OS2/1)
    - Furniture Styles, 1964 (Box-folder OS3/1)
- Gold Black Sand Mining Company, 1921-1936; Series II; 0.25 linear feet
  This series contains correspondence, legal, organizational, and research records generated by the Gold Black Sand Mining Company, a gold and platinum drilling and dredging operation on the Clark's Fork of the Yellowstone River in Montana. The business was headquartered in Great Falls, Montana. These materials highlight transformations in Montana's mineral extraction industry from placer mines to larger-scale, trace mineral recovery operations.
  - General Correspondence, 1923-1936; Subseries 1; 0.25 linear feet
    - 1923-1926 (Box-folder 85/7)